roger-waters.com 2013-10-20

# Privacy Policy « Roger Waters :: The Wall Live :: Official Site

641 Productions LLC is committed to protecting your privacy. Because your privacy is important to us, we have adopted and implemented this Privacy Policy as part of our commitment to protect your personal information. This policy covers both our offline and online collection practices.  Websites that are linked to our site may have different policies; please review the privacy policies on those sites for details.

By using and viewing www.Rogerwaters.com and all associated subdomains (the “Website(s)”), you accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions of Use.

641 Productions LLC complies with the privacy laws and regulations of the United States of America. 641 Productions LLC makes no representation that this Website is governed by or operated in accordance with the laws of other nations, or that the Website or any part thereof is appropriate or available for use in any particular jurisdiction. Those who choose to access the Website do so on their own initiative and at their own risk, and are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules and regulations. By using this Website, visitors from outside of the United States of America acknowledge this Website is subject to the laws and regulations of the United States of America, and waive any claims that may arise under their own national laws.

**What Information Is Collected on the Website  
**

• 641 Productions LLC collects the following information from you either during registration or as part of your use of the Website: first and last name, mobile phone number, email address, street address, password, and other information (“personal information”).  
• 641 Productions LLC may combine personal information that we have collected from you with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.  
• 641 Productions LLC automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, “cookies” (as defined below), and the pages you request.  
• We may also gather anonymous information, which may be used by us or shared with third parties. This is information which does not personally identify you, but which may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer.  
• The Website may place a small text file called a “cookie” on your computer’s hard drive for record keeping or other purposes. Although most web browsers automatically accept cookies, many computers allow you to change your browser setting to prevent acceptance of cookies, but you may not be able to enjoy all of the offerings of this Website. We do not set any personally identifiable information in cookies, nor do we employ any data capture mechanisms on our Website other than cookies.  
• We use the information we collect from you to allow you to participate in the site activities for which the information is collected.  For example, when you give us your email address in order to receive updates about Roger Waters, that address is added to the email list for Roger Waters.  On each email you receive, you are given the opportunity to unsubscribe; once you unsubscribe, you will no longer receive such emails.  
• We may send updates via SMS (text messages).  A cell phone number and carrier service provider is only required if you want to receive updates via SMS (text messages) sent to your mobile device.  There are usually costs associated with receiving SMS (text) messages depending on your wireless carrier and plan. You should check with your mobile carrier to determine what charges apply.

For contests conducted on this site, we use the personal information you provide only for the purpose of contacting you if you win a prize and sending the prize to you. We do not use contact information contained in contest entries to create mailing lists or for any other purpose, unless you have simultaneously subscribed to a mailing list. For further information about how we handle entries to a particular contest, please consult the contest rules.  To the extent such rules conflict with this privacy policy, such rules will govern that particular contest.

This Website will offer merchandise and/or ticket purchase services, which may be offered by us or by one of our e-commerce partners. To the extent the merchandise and/or ticket purchase services are offered by one of our e-commerce partners, such e-commerce partner will be collecting and using the information you provide.

To the extent 641 Productions LLC is the entity offering the purchase services, when you make a purchase through the Website, we may collect your credit card number or other payment account number (for example, your PayPal account number), billing address and other information related to such purchase from you. We will use the payment information that you provide to bill you for your purchase and to fulfill your purchase. By providing your payment information, you are authorizing us to give that information to third parties as necessary to confirm and fulfill your order (for example, to process your credit card or payment account number and to send you products you have ordered).

When you provide information to one of our Website’s e-commerce partners, vendors or advertisers, this transaction will occur in connection with the site of the e-commerce partner, vendor or advertiser, not on the Website, and, as such, the information you provide is collected pursuant to and controlled by the privacy policy of such e-commerce partner, vendor or advertiser. 641 Productions LLC is not responsible for such parties’ privacy policies and we encourage you to familiarize yourself with the applicable privacy policy of the e-commerce site with which you transact business or to contact the operator of such site for more information.

**What Information We Share and Disclose**

• 641 Productions LLC may share any personal information provided by you on this Website with its parents, subsidiaries, joint ventures or other companies under common control with 641 Productions LLC, in which case we will require such entities to honor this Privacy Policy.  
• We may share your email address with partners when you have agreed to receive communications from such partners.  
• 641 Productions LLC permits users to submit personal information for use in our Membership section. This information is stored for the purposes of member self-publishing and interaction; we may also use this information to customize your experience of our website.  
• From time to time, we may send you e-mail or text messages regarding promotional activities, events, products or new and special features on www.rogerwaters.com. We will always give you the ability to opt-out of receiving these promotional messages.  
• 641 Productions LLC does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or third parties or non-affiliated companies except when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:  
• We may provide personal information about you to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process and may disclose your information to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.  
• We may provide personal information about you when it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving actual or potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.  
• We may provide personal information about you in an emergency to protect the personal safety of users of our Website or the public.  
• We may provide personal information about you in the course of investigating allegations of misconduct or negligence on the part of any officer, employee, or agent of 641 Productions LLC.

**Editing Your Personal Information  
**

You can edit your  [tickets.rogerwaters.com](http://tickets.rogerwaters.com/ "Tickets at RogerWaters.com") registration profile at any time.

If you are under 13 years of age, you should not provide any personally identifiable information on this site without the knowledge and permission of your parent or guardian. There are certain web pages within our website that require users to be at least 13 years of age; these pages require you to enter your date of birth, and anyone under the age of 13 will be restricted from participating in such web page activities. We use cookies and/or web beacons to assure that this restriction persists. This may mean that you will be unable to participate in some activities on the site.

All contests that may be held on this site will be limited to persons above a certain age. Accordingly, we ask each contestant to provide year of birth, as well as name, address, and email address. Please refer to the specific age requirements for each contest as rules may vary from contest to contest.

**Public Forums**

We may make various public forums (such as blogs, and user forums) and functions available to you. During these activities, you will have the option to add additional personal information that is beyond the information gathered at registration. Any information you choose to share when using any of these forums or functions becomes public information. It is incumbent upon you to exercise caution in deciding whether to disclose such information.

We ask each visitor who wishes to participate in blogs, chat rooms and bulletin boards on this site to provide an email address along with the visitor’s screen name to access these functions. Each visitor who wishes to send a so-called “postcard” is asked to provide the visitor’s screen name and email address, the recipient’s name and email address, and a message selected by the visitor. Except for the uses described in the paragraphs above, all such email addresses are used only to protect the security and integrity of the site, such as to take action against visitors who post inappropriate material or harass other visitors. You are responsible and are deemed to have consented to disclosure if you post your email address or other identifying information to a publicly viewable interactive site application such as a blog, chat room or bulletin board.

**Opting Out**

If you do not want us to use your information as described above, you may choose not to provide us with your information by not registering with us or by modifying your information as provided below. If you choose not to provide us with personal information, you will not enjoy all of the services offered through the Website.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time in our sole discretion, by providing thirty (30) days notice to you by displaying a prominent notice, in all caps, above the text of the Privacy Policy. If we change this Privacy Policy, we will post the changes on our Website’s Privacy Policy page so that you will always know what type of personally identifiable information we collect and how we use this information. If you continue to use our Website following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy, you agree to be bound by the changes to the Privacy Policy.

**Security**

We maintain reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information we have collected about you, but these systems may not be completely secure from hackers, errors or interruptions in service. We use encrypted authentication technology when you login to www.rogerwaters.com in an effort to provide a secure environment that is protected from third party access, alteration, theft or misuse of the personal information you have provided.

**Contacting us**

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, our privacy practices, or your interaction with this Website, please contact us at [info@rogerwaters.com](mailto:info@rogerwaters.com).
